{
  "antonimy": [
    {
      "question": "машина",
      "answer": "человек"
    },
    {
      "question": "сердце",
      "answer": "разум"
    },
    {
      "question": "рукопись",
      "answer": "черновик"
    },
    {
      "question": "труд",
      "answer": "отдых"
    },
    {
      "question": "команда",
      "answer": "индивидуум"
    },
    {
      "question": "замок",
      "answer": "лачуга"
    },
    {
      "question": "великан",
      "answer": "мелочь"
    },
    {
      "question": "плач",
      "answer": "смех"
    },
    {
      "question": "правка",
      "answer": "порча"
    },
    {
      "question": "огонь",
      "answer": "вода"
    },
    {
      "question": "восход",
      "answer": "закат"
    },
    {
      "question": "добро",
      "answer": "зло"
    },
    {
      "question": "утро",
      "answer": "вечер"
    },
    {
      "question": "мир",
      "answer": "война"
    },
    {
      "question": "труженик",
      "answer": "бездельник"
    },
    {
      "question": "лето",
      "answer": "зима"
    },
    {
      "question": "друг",
      "answer": "враг"
    },
    {
      "question": "грусть",
      "answer": "радость"
    },
    {
      "question": "болтун",
      "answer": "молчун"
    },
    {
      "question": "храбрость",
      "answer": "трусость"
    },
    {
      "question": "молчать",
      "answer": "говорить"
    },
    {
      "question": "бежать",
      "answer": "стоять"
    },
    {
      "question": "радоваться",
      "answer": "огорчаться"
    },
    {
      "question": "стемнело",
      "answer": "рассвело"
    },
    {
      "question": "свет",
      "answer": "тьма"
    }
  ],
"paron":[
{
  "question": "абонемент",
  "answer": "абонент"
},
{
  "question": "абстрактность",
  "answer": "абстракция"
},
{
  "question": "авантюрин",
  "answer": "авантюрист"
},
{
  "question": "автобиографический",
  "answer": "автобиографичный"
},
{
  "question": "автоматический",
  "answer": "автоматичный"
},
{
  "question": "адресант",
  "answer": "адресат"
},
{
  "question": "академический",
  "answer": "академичный"
},
{
  "question": "аккордный",
  "answer": "аккордовый"
},
{
  "question": "бабий",
  "answer": "бабский"
},
{
  "question": "барский",
  "answer": "барственный"
},
{
  "question": "бедный",
  "answer": "бедственный"
},
{
  "question": "безделица",
  "answer": "бездельница"
},
{
  "question": "безликий",
  "answer": "безличный"
},
{
  "question": "безответный",
  "answer": "безответственный"
},
{
  "question": "безыскусный",
  "answer": "безыскусственный"
},
{
  "question": "белеть",
  "answer": "белить"
},
{
  "question": "вакансия",
  "answer": "вакация"
},
{
  "question": "вакхальный",
  "answer": "вакханальный"
},
{
  "question": "варкий",
  "answer": "варочный"
},
{
  "question": "вассальный",
  "answer": "вассальский"
},
{
  "question": "вафельница",
  "answer": "вафельщица"
},
{
  "question": "вбежать",
  "answer": "взбежать"
},
{
  "question": "вбить",
  "answer": "взбить"
},
{
  "question": "ввалить",
  "answer": "взвалить"
},
{
  "question": "гагарий",
  "answer": "гагаровый"
},
{
  "question": "гадальный",
  "answer": "гадательный"
},
{
  "question": "гарантийный",
  "answer": "гарантированный"
},
{
  "question": "дарёный",
  "answer": "даровой"
},
{
  "question": "дармоедный",
  "answer": "дармоедский"
},
{
  "question": "двигатель",
  "answer": "движитель"
}
  ],
  "sinonimy":[
    {
      "question": "машина",
      "answer": "механизм"
    },
    {
      "question": "сердце",
      "answer": "душа"
    },
  {
    "question": "кровать",
    "answer": "постель"
  },
  {
    "question": "рукопись",
    "answer": "манускрипт"
  },
  {
    "question": "труд",
    "answer": "дело"
  },
  {
    "question": "декламация",
    "answer": "чтение"
  },
  {
    "question": "экипаж",
    "answer": "команда"
  },
  {
    "question": "холст",
    "answer": "полотно"
  },
  {
    "question": "крепость",
    "answer": "замок"
  },
  {
    "question": "ковер",
    "answer": "палас"
  },
  {
    "question": "актуальный",
    "answer": "злободневный"
  },
  {
    "question": "аморальный",
    "answer": "безнравственный"
  },
  {
    "question": "анализ",
    "answer": "разбор"
  },
  {
    "question": "антураж",
    "answer": "окружение"
  },
  {
    "question": "аргумент",
    "answer": "довод"
  },	
  {
    "question": "бизнес",
    "answer": "дело"
  },
  {
    "question": "брифинг",
    "answer": "летучка"
  },
  {
    "question": "вариант",
    "answer": "разновидность"
  },
  {
    "question": "габариты",
    "answer": "размеры"
  },
  {
    "question": "герметичный",
    "answer": "непроницаемый"
  },
  {
    "question": "гипотетический",
    "answer": "предположительный"
  },
  {
    "question": "голкипер",
    "answer": "вратарь"
  },
  {
    "question": "детальный",
    "answer": "подробный"
  },
  {
    "question": "диалог",
    "answer": "беседа"
  },
  {
    "question": "директор",
    "answer": "управляющий"
  }
  ]
}